xosara.com 2017-12-12

# About Us, Privacy Policy and Terms of Use on Xosara.com

### ABOUT US

Xosara.com launched in December 2012 after a 3 year wait period. Its aim is to collect all the great girls fashion games around and to display them in a fresh new website, child friendly and updated daily with the latest findings. 

* * *

### TERMS OF USE

By entering Xosara.com you herby accept the following: 

  1. Xosara.com is a free to enter website
  2. By enterting and browsing Xosara.com you accept to respect any of the rules posted on this page
  3. You will use this website as is
  4. Xosara.com and its owners will not be held responsible for any data loss or damage you might experience while browsing our website 
  5. All games are free to play until further notice
  6. All games belong to their respective owners and Xosara.com will not take any responsibility for their content 
  7. We check each game individually in order to have safe content published, but if you feel we missed anything please write us an email using the email below. 
  8. The website's design, logo and colors are Copyrighted and are owned by Xosara.com and its owners and you cannot use it without our written agreement. 

* * *

### PRIVACY POLICY

The following is the official privacy policy for **xosara.com** , a website centered around flash games and child-friendly content. This Privacy Policy covers the issues related to personal information collected by the Site and information regarding tracking and information collection from our affiliates, advertisers and partners. 

### Acknowledgement and acceptance of terms

**xosara.com** is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement explains what information we collect when you interact with our website. By accessing **xosara.com** , you acknowledge and fully understand **xosara.com** 's Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement. 

### Collection of Personal Information

Visitors are required to be 13 years or older to register. If not they must be accompanied by a parent or guardian who is directly supervising them. If you are not 13 years of age, have your parents review these Terms of Use and after receiving their consent, you have the right to use the games published on xosara.com.

**NOTICE For Parents:**  
We do not collect any personal identifiable information and the tools we use to track our website's performance are: Google Analytics, DFP Small Business, Compete.com and QuantCast.

All the external links from the games have been closed in order to protect our users from potential harmful URL destinations. We may decide to open the links to some of the games if we consider the destination to be safe for our users. At **xosara.com** , we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important and we take every measure to keep you informed on how we collect, safeguard and use your personal data, where applicable. We never sell your personal information to third parties, however our site might run scripts (such as Google Analytics) that collect log file information for analytical and statistical reports. The kind of information these third parties collect include your IP address, your ISP ( Internet Service Provider), the browser you visit our site with (Firefox, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Safari, etc), the pages you visit and the time you spend on pages of our site. This information is used strictly for ourselves, using it to better improve our site's performance and user experience. We will never sell your personal information to third parties. 

### Use of Collected Information

**xosara.com** collects certain information from and about its users in 3 ways: directly from Google Analytics and by using Facebook (when logged in). We may track information about visits to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include: Your Internet protocol address. 

  * The kind of browser or computer you use.
  * Number of links you click within the site.
  * State or country from which you accessed the site.
  * Date and time of your visit.
  * Name of your Internet service provider.
  * Referring website.
  * Pages you viewed on the site.

### Online Behavioral Advertising

**xosara.com** uses OBA for several of its ad blocks. OBA is based on a set of principles encouraging consumer-friendly standards in online advertising such as educating the user about the ads he will see, transparency in regards to their placement and data security for the user browsing our web pages. The Advertising Networks that we use adhere to these standards as well. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Our Online Behavioral Advertising compliant partners might use cookies and web beacons through their ads. Cookies are small text files that are placed in the visitor's computer with the purpose of storing their preferences. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user's hard drive, they are purely "shortcuts" that allow websites to remember users activities on a web site as well as users visits to a site. Since we use third party advertisements to support **xosara.com** , there is a chance the companies running these ads might store your data in cookies, in order to collect advertisement information or to protect you from abusive advertising (for example, stopping pop-up scripts from running multiple times from your IP). Because these advertising companies may also collect the personal information, we at **xosara.com** make sure we only use trustworthy 3rd parties, in order to protect our users. **xosara.com** is displaying advertisements on the game pages, ads from Google Adsense, ValueClick Media, CPM Star and other advertising vendors. Google offers child safe targeted ads to our users. Google is also using the DART cookie to collect information about every user. This cookie does not store any personal data or sensitive information and can be removed by you searching the cookie in the cookies folder of your browser on your PC. If you as a parent or as a user find ads that are not appropriate for children please notify us at once. In general, these cookies and web beacons are used for research purposes and for geo-targeting and behavioral targeting of the ads. If you feel uncomfortable providing this kind of information to our advertisers through cookies, you can turn them off from your preferred browser's settings, or manage them through Internet Security software (such as Norton Internet Security for example). 

### External Links

Our site has several external links pointing to our partners, or the flash games we post on our site might have in-game links to other sites that might offer content that we have no control over. Unfortunately, we cannot take responsibility for the content shown by our partners, although we only pick to link to related, quality websites that are non-intrusive and offer clean content suitable for our target audience. 

Advertising on **xosara.com** offers advertisement places in several places across the website. These ad spots show Google Adsense Ads, ValueClick Media or other ads and are child friendly. If you wish to advertise on our website, please use your Google Adwords account to book a spot in the ad places as they can be targeted for advertising or email us at:  

### Opt out Mechanism

All sites using advertisements provided by companies that adhered to the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) must provide an opt-out button that will allow users to no longer receive online advertising. In order to opt out from the advertisements provided by our NAI compliant partners, please use the opt-out form provided by the organization by [clicking here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

**xosara.com** reserves the right to change this policy at any time. We ask that you review this Privacy Policy from time to time to insure you are familiar with the most current version of it. 

* * *

### CONTACT US

In order to facilitate communication please write us an email at the email address presented above and we'll do our best to get back to you in a timely manner. 

Game submissions will be also done via emails so please send us each of your games only once. More emails sent with the same game will result in us banning your IP and server.

Thank you.
